DAVID CHA

david.cha874@icloud.com 0450 634 700

Career Profile

I am an experienced individual with face-to-face customer service history and emphasis on empathetic approach to negotiations. Effective and efficient collaborator with internal and external stakeholders. Detail driven and adept at working within a team environment – backed by interpersonal skills and a determination to succeed.

Employment History

13cabs, Sydney NSW – Partner Growth Specialist

October 2019 to Present

- Implemented new workflow that grew 450 NDIS and Working with Children clearance accredited Driver Clients in 12 months (Process adopted offices interstate)
- Maintaining Database of Driver Clients and validity of NDIS and Working with Children documents
- Implemented improved workflow and company policy that transitioned over 40+ Driver Clients to Silver Service (Process adopted offices interstate)
- Generated revenue by onboarding over 130+ Operator Clients and Taxi vehicles.

13cabs, Sydney NSW – Contact Centre Agent

November 2014 to October 2019

- Achievied 90% KPIs in providing a pleasant and efficient experience to customer calls in a high volume call centre bookings, service enquiries and complaints
- Allocation and management of drivers to bookings Liaising with Team Leaders in tracking Taxi Etas, vehicle attributes and large volume broadcast of Taxi services.
- Supervising regional branch taxi services
- Liaising with account holders to dispatch large batch Taxi bookings

Extracurricular

TEDxUNSW, UNSW Sydney Kensington NSW | 2016 September 2016(Camera Operations) | 2017 January to 2017 October (Productions Manager)

- Liaison with stakeholders for the development of promotional video content to be placed on social media platforms such as Facebook, Instagram and Youtube
- Managing production pipeline from initial stages of Pre-production to Production to Post production
- Responsible for Treatments, scripts and Production schedule
- Completion of UNSW Art & Design Professional Experience with TedxUNSW

Education

Bachelor of Media Arts (Honours)

2014 to 2017

University of New South Wales, Darlinghurst NSW

Professional Skills

Languages: English – Fluent, Korean – Fluent

Technical Skills: MTI, Telnet, Internal CRM, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Dynamics 365

Soft Skills: Emotional intelligence, good time management, strong interpersonal skill, adaptable and versatile

Referees upon request